{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819052763","data":{"timestamp":" 947819052762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" c7024059-a936-4d5c-882a-5867e75a506b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819058733","data":{"timestamp":" 947819058733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" c7024059-a936-4d5c-882a-5867e75a506b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819064730","data":{"timestamp":" 947819064730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" c7024059-a936-4d5c-882a-5867e75a506b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819067041","data":{"timestamp":" 947819067041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" c7024059-a936-4d5c-882a-5867e75a506b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819079991","data":{"timestamp":" 947819079990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819083773","data":{"timestamp":" 947819083772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819085346","data":{"timestamp":" 947819085346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819089191","data":{"timestamp":" 947819089191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819090757","data":{"timestamp":" 947819090756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819096032","data":{"timestamp":" 947819096032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819097631","data":{"timestamp":" 947819097631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819103397","data":{"timestamp":" 947819103397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819105000","data":{"timestamp":" 947819105000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819111280","data":{"timestamp":" 947819111280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819112844","data":{"timestamp":" 947819112843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819121839","data":{"timestamp":" 947819121839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819123396","data":{"timestamp":" 947819123396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819129551","data":{"timestamp":" 947819129550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819131164","data":{"timestamp":" 947819131164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819135015","data":{"timestamp":" 947819135015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819136607","data":{"timestamp":" 947819136606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819144168","data":{"timestamp":" 947819144167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819145753","data":{"timestamp":" 947819145753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819150977","data":{"timestamp":" 947819150977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819152569","data":{"timestamp":" 947819152569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819157049","data":{"timestamp":" 947819157049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819159056","data":{"timestamp":" 947819159055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819159229","data":{"timestamp":" 947819159229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" efa7149c-ef4c-4fc5-a2a4-ae23db8d3f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819170970","data":{"timestamp":" 947819170970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 5c5a8a6a-2037-4c1b-bcf6-253b97de2f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819175334","data":{"timestamp":" 947819175333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 5c5a8a6a-2037-4c1b-bcf6-253b97de2f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819176876","data":{"timestamp":" 947819176875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 5c5a8a6a-2037-4c1b-bcf6-253b97de2f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819183720","data":{"timestamp":" 947819183720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 5c5a8a6a-2037-4c1b-bcf6-253b97de2f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" START_ANDAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819190114","data":{"timestamp":" 947819190114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 5c5a8a6a-2037-4c1b-bcf6-253b97de2f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819191701","data":{"timestamp":" 947819191701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 5c5a8a6a-2037-4c1b-bcf6-253b97de2f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819193186","data":{"timestamp":" 947819193186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 5c5a8a6a-2037-4c1b-bcf6-253b97de2f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819193262","data":{"timestamp":" 947819193262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 5c5a8a6a-2037-4c1b-bcf6-253b97de2f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819250544","data":{"timestamp":" 947819250543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 56fe2875-4737-4795-87fe-4d1bb7c78708"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819257349","data":{"timestamp":" 947819257349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 56fe2875-4737-4795-87fe-4d1bb7c78708"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819258889","data":{"timestamp":" 947819258889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 56fe2875-4737-4795-87fe-4d1bb7c78708"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819264508","data":{"timestamp":" 947819264508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 56fe2875-4737-4795-87fe-4d1bb7c78708"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819266077","data":{"timestamp":" 947819266077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 56fe2875-4737-4795-87fe-4d1bb7c78708"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819268037","data":{"timestamp":" 947819268036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 56fe2875-4737-4795-87fe-4d1bb7c78708"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819268193","data":{"timestamp":" 947819268193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 56fe2875-4737-4795-87fe-4d1bb7c78708"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819275294","data":{"timestamp":" 947819275294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 56fe2875-4737-4795-87fe-4d1bb7c78708"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819283469","data":{"timestamp":" 947819283469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 56fe2875-4737-4795-87fe-4d1bb7c78708"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819300656","data":{"timestamp":" 947819300656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 25917d06-293a-4b9b-b786-6fa303223696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-8-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819301739","data":{"timestamp":" 947819301738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 25917d06-293a-4b9b-b786-6fa303223696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-8-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819307128","data":{"timestamp":" 947819307126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 25917d06-293a-4b9b-b786-6fa303223696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-8-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819313197","data":{"timestamp":" 947819313197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 25917d06-293a-4b9b-b786-6fa303223696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-8-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819320991","data":{"timestamp":" 947819320991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 25917d06-293a-4b9b-b786-6fa303223696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-8-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819331768","data":{"timestamp":" 947819331767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 25917d06-293a-4b9b-b786-6fa303223696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-8-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819370115","data":{"timestamp":" 947819370115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 2b8b014a-5eeb-4db3-b823-a8b799326c0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819386134","data":{"timestamp":" 947819386134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 2b8b014a-5eeb-4db3-b823-a8b799326c0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819398376","data":{"timestamp":" 947819398375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 2b8b014a-5eeb-4db3-b823-a8b799326c0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819403066","data":{"timestamp":" 947819403066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 2b8b014a-5eeb-4db3-b823-a8b799326c0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819427107","data":{"timestamp":" 947819427107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 2b8b014a-5eeb-4db3-b823-a8b799326c0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819835544","data":{"timestamp":" 947819835543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" ad969504-c0b5-4bf6-8fae-e3b3d9af8f25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819846951","data":{"timestamp":" 947819846951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" ad969504-c0b5-4bf6-8fae-e3b3d9af8f25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819852845","data":{"timestamp":" 947819852845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" ad969504-c0b5-4bf6-8fae-e3b3d9af8f25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819861873","data":{"timestamp":" 947819861873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" ad969504-c0b5-4bf6-8fae-e3b3d9af8f25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819863605","data":{"timestamp":" 947819863605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" ad969504-c0b5-4bf6-8fae-e3b3d9af8f25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819889828","data":{"timestamp":" 947819889828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 86cb862e-d928-494d-8867-fceccb5cac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819901725","data":{"timestamp":" 947819901725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 86cb862e-d928-494d-8867-fceccb5cac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819914322","data":{"timestamp":" 947819914322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 86cb862e-d928-494d-8867-fceccb5cac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819920077","data":{"timestamp":" 947819920077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 86cb862e-d928-494d-8867-fceccb5cac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819927736","data":{"timestamp":" 947819927736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 86cb862e-d928-494d-8867-fceccb5cac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Add single digits no carry"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947819935821","data":{"timestamp":" 947819935821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 86cb862e-d928-494d-8867-fceccb5cac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947823267495","data":{"timestamp":" 947823267495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 86cb862e-d928-494d-8867-fceccb5cac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947823272971","data":{"timestamp":" 947823272970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 86cb862e-d928-494d-8867-fceccb5cac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947823279328","data":{"timestamp":" 947823279328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 86cb862e-d928-494d-8867-fceccb5cac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.0..9.AllCarryBorrow.lev9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_1+9=10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947824712262","data":{"timestamp":" 947824712262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 16d5366a-e508-46ca-b9bc-9173e85dbb12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947824718208","data":{"timestamp":" 947824718208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_060346"," gameId":" 16d5366a-e508-46ca-b9bc-9173e85dbb12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}